[
  {
    "question": "Name a few beneficial microbes for the environment",
    "answer": "Rhizobacteria and micorrhizal fungi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the sustainable transit modes?",
    "answer": "Biking, Walking, Public Transit"
  },
  {
    "question": "Examples of renewable energies?",
    "answer": "Solar, wind, biogas"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's methane?",
    "answer": "A greenhouse gas 84 times more potent than CO2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where's Pacific Regional Park?",
    "answer": "On the UBC Campus"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many metro parks in Vancouver?",
    "answer": "Close to 200"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name a few invasive species in BC",
    "answer": "Blueweed, Butterfly Bush, Canada Thistle ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "What's zero waste?",
    "answer": "All products can be redesigned and reused"
  },
  {
    "question": "Aspects of sustainable buildings?",
    "answer": "Long life-cycle and system durability"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is climate the same as weather?",
    "answer": "No. Climate is long-term."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does sustainability mean?",
    "answer": "The capacity of humans and planet to co-exist"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the Paris Agreement about?",
    "answer": "Climate Change"
  }
]
